const grade3data=[
    {
        question:"break",
        choices:["ブレーキをかける","消える","解散する","壊す"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"boil",
        choices:["沸騰する","蒸発する","かき混ぜる","温める"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"clever",
        choices:["利口な","謙虚な","天才的な","独創的な"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"dining",
        choices:["台所","食事","夕食","調理"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"impossible",
        choices:["不必要な","不審な","不可欠な","不可能な"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"help yourself",
        choices:["相手を助ける","進展させる","手伝う","ご自由にどうぞ"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question:"take part in",
        choices:["参加する","出席する","追加する","取り出す"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"up to",
        choices:["～次第で","～のせいで","～のおかげで","～によると"],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:"stand for",
        choices:["立ち上がる","～を表す","～に寄りかかる","そばにいる"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"before long",
        choices:["はるか昔に","最近","すでに","まもなく"],
        answer:3
    }
]

export default grade3data;